<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title>All Posts - Wildanoo Site</title>
        <link>http://wildanoo.com/posts/</link>
        <description>All Posts | Wildanoo Site</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 16:00:59 &#43;0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://wildanoo.com/posts/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
    <title>Create and Deploy Website for Free With Hugo</title>
    <link>http://wildanoo.com/create-and-deploy-website-for-free-with-hugo/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 16:00:59 &#43;0700</pubDate>
    <author>WildanAB</author>
    <guid>http://wildanoo.com/create-and-deploy-website-for-free-with-hugo/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Nowadays have a website for our portfolio or blogging is necessary to improve our digital presence and share our interest to the world. Fortunately there are a lot of options to create our own website from paid to free.
This time I want to share how to create website with hugo for free. Hugo is one of the most popular open-source static site generators, it use golang as its language which make it the fastest framework for building website.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Using Http In Git Just Like SSH</title>
    <link>http://wildanoo.com/using-github-bitbucket/</link>
    <pubDate>Tue, 23 May 2023 15:53:18 &#43;0700</pubDate>
    <author>WildanAB</author>
    <guid>http://wildanoo.com/using-github-bitbucket/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[<div class="featured-image">
                <img src="/images/featured/github-cover.png" referrerpolicy="no-referrer">
            </div>Common practice in cloning and work around git is using SSH, but sometimes setup SSH is a daunting task and troublesome especially for beginner. There is another way to work around git without using SSH that is using HTTPS. If you&rsquo;re stuck when setup SSH by facing error that you can&rsquo;t solve, I encourage you to use HTTPS, it&rsquo;s not a shame to use HTTPS just take it easy. This approach feels more straight to the point to setup and run git.]]></description>
</item>
<item>
    <title>Introduction</title>
    <link>http://wildanoo.com/1_post/</link>
    <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2023 21:27:08 &#43;0700</pubDate>
    <author>WildanAB</author>
    <guid>http://wildanoo.com/1_post/</guid>
    <description><![CDATA[Hi and welcome.. This website supposed to be my main site for sharing information related to software development. More content are on the way and also you can check my social media which not that social and my portfolio here, later.
Godspeed!]]></description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>
